

Bernat Felip I Díaz

063 457 438 | E: Bernat.felip1@gmail.com Carrer De Sor Eulàlia D'Anzizu, Barcelona, Spain 08034

PROFESSIONAL (**SUMMARY**

I've always been a very ambitious and hard working person, this is why I am currently studying a double bachelor degree. I consider myself to be very hard-working and passionate with what I do.

SKILLS ()

the fact that I'm currently studying a double degree. I consider myself to be very hard-working, I do not tire easily and I Expertise on a wide range of will not stop the work until what I planned to do is finished. **Confident** person with the ability to communicate with security.

Exceptional time management, given Attended multiple soft skills trainings, including motivation, communication, delegation, project monitoring, leadership, etc.

programming languages, such as C, C++, Python, JavaScript, SQL, Java, Haskell, Prolog, etc.

WORK HISTORY

BACKEND DEVELOPER

07/2018 to 09/2018

Goin | Barcelona, Spain

Worked together with the rest of the development team to implement and document backend microservices of an app using TypeScript and Python.

INTERNSHIP

07/2017 to 09/2017

HP | Sant Cugat del Vallès, Spain

Developed and documented a testing tool for backend server-frontentprinter communication using Python.

EDUCATION

Bachelor Degree | Informatics Engineering Universitat Politècnica De Catalunya, Barcelona, Spain 8.11 average grade.

Bachelor Degree | Telecommunications Engineering 2020 Universitat Politècnica De Catalunya, Barcelona, Spain 7.9/10 average grade.

Technological Baccalaureate

2015

2020

Escola BetàniaPatmos, Barcelona, Spain

- Graduated with 9.73/10 final grade.
- 13.32/14 on the University Access Exam.

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Entered CFIS (Centre de Formació Interdisciplinària Superior) in 2016 which pays for my second degree in university.

Premi Extraordinari de la Selectivitat (2015): For getting more than a 9/10 in the general part of the University Access Exam I received a special mention.

Graduated with honors from baccalaureate (2015), which paid for my first year of university.

Recipient of University Aid scholarship (2015) from "Fundació-Catalunya-La Pedrera" due to my good grades during Baccalaureate and at the University Access Exam.

Secretary General of a simulated MUN (Model United Nations) in school (2014): Ten other students and me voluntarily organized a Model United Nations for the students of 4th of ESO.

Scholarship to participate in MUNOG (Model United Nations of Goldberg) 2013 in Sindelfingen (Stuttgart, Germany): This is a simulation of a United Nations conference and I was acting as the ambassador of Guatemala in the Security Council, debating on the topic of the Syrian Conflict.

LANGUAGES ()

First Certificate in English (Obtained in December, 2012). Mark: 78% Certificate in Advanced English (Obtained in March, 2014). Mark: 84% Certificate of Proficiency in English (Obtained in March, 2015). Mark: 219

DELF (A2, French). Mark: 98% DALF (B1, French). Mark: 89%

Former federate player of BM La Roca. I played handball since I was 3 years old up until 2017. I believe taking part in team sports aids you toward truly teamworking in the future.

Member of universitary student organization BEST-UPC (Board of European Students of Technology). An association which offers students complementary education and aids them in acquiring a more international mentality. During my stay in this association I have had many different responsibilities:

- Participants Responsible of Autumn Course 2017 : each year we organize a course on technology which students from all over Europe attend and I was the main responsible for their wellbeing and all social activities during the course.
- IT Coordinator 2017-2018 : in the association we have different departments to separate de work we do during the year and I was responsible for coordinating all the IT team.
- Main Organizer of Autumn Course 2018: I had to coordinate all the different responsibles of the course and make sure everything went according to plan.
- Treasurer 2018-2019: I am currently the treasurer of the association, I am responsible for the balances of our accounts, declaring taxes, budgets, etc.

AFFILIATIONS (

COMPLEMENTARY EDUCATION

5th of Intermediate Degree: Piano . I attended weekly piano lessons for 12 years in the music school of Escola Betània Patmos.

4th of Intermediate Degree: Music Education . I attended two weekly hours of music theory for 12 years.

Attended a **10-day course on robotics in Warsaw** organized by the student organization BEST (1.5 ECTS). (July 2016)

Attended a **10-day course on Android Development** in Barcelona organized by the student organization BMA (2 ECTS). (January 2017)

Attended **ACM International Collegiate Programming Contest Bootcamp** in Harbour Space University (Barcelona, January 2017). It was a preparation for the actual programming contest.

Attended **small course on Machine Learning** offered to CFIS students (February 2017).

Attended a **10-day course on 3D Printing in Ghent** organized by the student organization BEST (1.5 ECTS). (July 2017)